goophoneshops.com 2019-04-21

# Privacy Policy - Official Goophone Shop

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to tell you what kind of information we may gather about you when you visit our site, how we may use that information and whether we disclose it to anyone. Our goal is to provide you with a satisfying online experience while allowing you to purchase products online knowing that your information is secure and not passed on to any 3rd Parties.

## COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

Information is collected only when you place an order or sign up to our mailing list. When placing an order you will be asked to provide information such as your name, postal address, email address, phone number. We require these details so we can send your order to you and contact you if we have any issues in doing so.

If you sign up to our mailing list or Opt in to recieve “marketing material” when placing an order we wil use your information to inform you of additional products, deals and services which may interest you. You can unsubscribe from this list at any time.

## USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will only use the personal information you have chosen to provide us for the purpose for which you provided it. We will not use your information for any other purpose without your consent.

## NO SALE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Under no circumstances will we sell or receive payment for licensing or disclosing your personal information.

## CARDHOLDER INFORMATION

We do not store or have access to your credit card details. We use PayPal as our payment gateway,therefore your card information may be collected by PayPal. To further secure your card information, SSL session is used to encript your personal information so that it is quite difficult for the hackers to steal your information during purchase.

## LINKS

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

## GOOGLE ANALYTICS

Our store may use Google Analytics to help us learn about who visits our site and what pages are being looked at.

## COOKIES

Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.

_session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows our system to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).

cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.

_secure_session_id, unique token, sessional

storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.

Google analytics:

PREF, persistent for a very short period, Set by Google and tracks who visits the store and from where

## AGE OF CONSENT

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

## CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

## QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at support#goophoneshops.com (please replace # with @).
